All of you are
wicked friends [laughs] let the water go and
first the pakodas.  Hey friend, it is very deep, please pour some water on it.
Hey friend, I have never found any water to drink in my life.  I will
die with such dedication that I will send you to grandmother's
village.  Are you giving water
?  Hey friend, there is less turmeric.  Bring turmeric.
[laughter]
Hey, what have you done?  You asked me to
add turmeric so I added it.  Hey friend, I
told you to put it in gram flour, not in the pan.
You will drive me crazy.  There
is less salt too, no salt.
Is salt okay?  I have asked you to check it.
You both cannot stay at home peacefully.  Let
me make it.  Take the salt.
You guys make it yourself.  Eat alone.
Hey friend, you entered and left.   Do
n't stop, friend.  Let me cook.
See how it is made.
got it?